-(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(CRICKETS CHITTERING)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
MICHAEL: Caroline,
open this door and let me in.
-(BABY CRYING)
-You are not taking my baby.
MICHAEL: It's a monster.
I will fucking shoot you!
-MICHAEL: Trust me, it's what must be done.
-(BREATHES SHAKILY)
You have to give up the baby.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Michael!
-(MICHAEL GROANS)
-(LOUD THUDDING)
I'm coming out.
I will shoot anyone
who comes near me!
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(BABY COOS)
(DOOR OPENS, CREAKS)
CAROLINE: Michael!
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
Michael!
(SOBS)
(BABY CRYING)
(SOBS, BREATHES HEAVILY)
Do you believe now?
-(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
-(MUSIC RISES)
-(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(BIRDS CHIRPING)
IAN: How's it look now?
-(WATER GUSHES)
-(FAUCET SQUEAKS)
Yeah,
if we bathed our baby in this,
people will come and take it.
(CHUCKLES)
(METAL RATTLING IN DISTANCE)
IAN: Stella? Try it again.
-(FAUCET SQUEAKS)
-(WATER GUSHES)
It's still hell's bathwater.
Oh! Oh no, it's clearing.
(SIGHS)
-Ah!
-Look at that.
(CHUCKLES)
It almost looks like
water's supposed to.
I think this technically
makes me a plumber.
How many YouTube videos
did you have to watch
to learn that?
Just one.
And five more.
-(CHUCKLES)
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
These are great.
I'm not sure
what I wanna do over the crib.
Maybe we can go
into the countryside
when the leaves turn,
get some pictures.
Yeah? It's a date.
Speaking of dates, uh,
the shower's a month away,
and you still haven't touched
your stack of invitations.
(SIGHS) Construction guys
aren't that into parties
where the food is miniaturized.
Pizza for dinner? I'm starving.
Oh, smooth, smooth deflection.
You said "pizza"
and my whole world
became cheese and pepperoni.
IAN: Mm.
I'm not talking
about your work mates,
and you know it.
Your family's about to get
a new member.
If a baby isn't reason enough
to reach out
after all these years--
The last thing
that we want is my family
anywhere near this kid's life.
It's best for everyone,
trust me.
Are you ever gonna tell me
what your issue is with them?
Hey, do you mind
putting the order in,
so it's here when I get back?
-What are you in the mood for?
-Ah. I don't know. Surprise me.
(INHALES SHARPLY) Oh. Oh.
Someone's doing somersaults.
Come here, feel.
(INTRICATE MUSIC PLAYING)
Ian.
(BREATHES NERVOUSLY)
Makes it all feel...
very real.
Ian?
Babe, what's wrong?
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
Nothing. I... I should go.
I need to drop this gear off
before they shut the place.
Let the water run
for another 20 minutes
and then turn it off, okay?
(DOOR OPENING)
-(THUNDER RUMBLING)
-(RAIN PATTERS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
STELLA: Can you say something?
Are you sure?
I had a vasectomy,
for God's sake.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GRUNTS)
(RAIN PATTERS)
STELLA: Ian. Babe, what's wrong?
Are you gonna tell me
what your issue is with them?
(SCREAMS)
-(TIRES SCREECH)
-(CAR CRASHES)
(THUNDERING RUMBLING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(GRAVEL CRUNCHING)
(APPLE THUDS)
CAROLINE:
Let me help you with that.
Um, thank you.
-Sorry, do we--
-Know each other?
No, not yet,
but I am hoping to change that.
I'm Caroline Cadell.
-Ian's mother.
-(INTRICATE MUSIC PLAYING)
If now isn't a good time,
I can--
-No, no, come in please.
-(KEYS JANGLING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
It's a lovely house.
It's got good ...
bones.
We were gonna fix it up.
We were gonna do
a lot of things.
Oh, sorry, can I get you
something to drink?
(MUSIC FADES)
-Uh, yes, a glass of water.
-Okay.
In other circumstances,
I'd say we both deserve
a shot of whiskey.
(CHUCKLES)
Let's, uh, go outside.
-Oh, yeah. Let me help you with that.
-Oh, thank you.
Yeah, please, you must sit down.
Your feet must be screaming.
-(STELLA CHUCKLES)
-Mine swelled worse with every pregnancy.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You're probably wondering
how I found you.
Imagining some sleazy
private investigator
who's... (CHUCKLES)
...following your every move.
(REFLECTIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GLASS CLINK)
But the truth is...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
...we stopped looking for Ian
a long time ago.
Yeah, when he decided to leave.
I can't change it now.
All those arguments
that I practiced in my head,
they're completely useless.
(SIGHS)
But you are here.
And I would love
to get to know you.
The woman that my son loved.
How did you know that he...
My son-in-law, he stumbled
across the obit online.
Ian, of course, had changed
his last name to Clark.
But then there was the photo.
He looked so handsome.
And happy.
I took that photo
on our honeymoon.
I wanted to contact you.
But I never knew
Ian's old last name.
Yes, I'm sure
he hid his past very well.
(GLASS THUDS)
(INHALES SHARPLY) Was the, um...
was the funeral nice? (CHUCKLES)
It was a small service,
just a few friends.
Your family didn't go?
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
It was just my mom
and I growing up.
Well, she died
when I was in college.
So, you're all alone?
Is it a boy or a girl?
We didn't want to know.
(SNIFFLES)
We thought it would be
a nice surprise.
Yes, well, babies come
with enough surprises.
Stella...
my children are all coming to
the summer cottage this weekend.
And I would love it...
if you would join us.
-If it's a family thing, I... I...
-(PAPER TEARING)
You have the last piece
of my son inside you.
That makes you family.
Please.
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BELL TOLLING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Cottage? (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
If you say so.
(GRAVEL CRUNCHING)
(PANTS)
Whoa, okay.
(GRAVEL CRUNCHING SOFTLY)
(MUSIC FADES)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
(SHARP EXHALE)
STELLA: Oh. Do you want me
to pee in your bushes?
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLES)
-Hello.
-(DOOR CREAKS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER STEREO IN DISTANCE)
Hello. Anyone home?
LAKE: I can't believe
we're having
this conversation again.
FELIX: What do you mean again?
LAKE: What do I mean?
Fifty grand, down the drain!
FELIX: We agreed
I can spend as I see fit.
LAKE: You know,
spending and squandering
-are not the same thing!
-FELIX: It's my money, Lake.
-Your allowance, you mean.
-FELIX: We agreed not to use that word.
-You agreed not to use it.
-Look, you don't know,
-the investment might still pay off.
-Like all your other investments?
FELIX:
If you really wanna use booze
as an excuse
for being a bitch, sweetie,
you should really try
and drink it first.
Or maybe I should
just dump it on the floor.
I mean, that's
what gets you off, isn't it?
Wasting my money.
Oh, what's this,
about 20 quid's worth?
-Shall I make it a double, hmm?
-(STELLA CLEARS THROAT)
Sorry. I'm... I'm so sorry.
I... I did knock,
but no one answered,
and I...
I really need the bathroom.
-I'm Stella.
-Yeah, yeah, we know. We all Googled you.
Nice LinkedIn pic.
-So, you do know what a job site is?
-Chew glass.
How about I pour this on my feet
and you lap it up like a puppy?
Oh, please don't get
any whiskey on the oriental.
You can still say that
about rugs, I hope. Hello.
Save the casual racism
for dinner, shall we, Mother?
She has to pee.
(BREATHES DEEPLY) Yeah.
-Curse of pregnancy. (CHUCKLES)
-Yes, one of them.
It's just down the hall
on the left.
Okay.
Are you serious?
-LAKE: What?
-Keep it together.
(TOILET FLUSHING)
(GASPS) Oh.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
The water was smooth as silk.
Weatherman said
it was gonna be scorching today.
-Shows what they know.
-You must be freezing.
Cold is good for the soul,
and you can withstand anything
if you put your mind to it.
I used to tell Ian that
when he had the
night terrors as a boy.
Did he ever grow out of them?
Perhaps, you...
perhaps, you should go
and get ready for dinner.
-(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
-You're worried she'll run,
screaming at the sight
of my nylon-clad bosom.
She looks tougher than that.
CAROLINE: She's a bit of
a character, Grandma Odette.
-The children call her Granno.
-Your mother?
My late husband's.
Come with me.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(PANTING)
I've put you in Ian's old room.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
It's a bit further
away than the others,
but I thought you might
like that, the privacy.
Oh, and it has an en suite.
I should get you
some fresh towels.
It's the help's week off.
Most of his things
have been put away in boxes now.
Rugby trophies... (CHUCKLES)
...those awful band posters,
video games.
Other things that I just
couldn't bear to put away.
(SIGHS)
No matter
what he told you, Stella.
It wasn't all bad.
It's happy memories.
Good times.
Families are complicated.
Dinner's at 7:00.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
-FELIX: How's that drink, Granno?
-(CUTLERY CLINKING)
-GRANNO: Mm. It's nice.
-(LAKE CHUCKLES)
GRANNO: I don't usually
like things with lemon,
-but this is okay.
-(LAKE CHUCKLES)
CAROLINE:
Has anybody heard from him?
I mean we've got time,
but we've just gotta make sure
that Stella
doesn't get suspicious.
LAKE: I hope
things stay on schedule.
-I really can't be away from the firm forever.
-(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
You work too much.
It's affecting your complexion.
Thanks, Granno.
Felix takes enough time off
for the both of us,
-don't you, darling?
-Did you want bitters in your tonic,
or do you just produce
them naturally?
-(KISSES)
-Felix!
Cadell babies come early,
and she does look close.
LAKE: I wouldn't worry.
Ian always did go
for the Pollyannas.
-Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho. Merry Christmas!
-(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS) It's summer, darling.
Well, Santa spent
the Lord's b-day
with a raging hangover,
but he's here now.
-(PLASTIC BAG CRUMPLES)
-Sister of mine, present for thee.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
-(GRANNO LAUGHS)
-(GASPS)
Is this new or did you
try it out for me?
-Oh, aren't you hysterical? Mwah, mwah.
-(BLOWS KISSES)
BUNNY: And what
have we got for Felix?
It's an old bottle of scotch.
Half empty, but you're used
to living off Lake's scraps, eh?
(LAUGHS)
GRANNO: Oh, it's so good
to have our Benjamin Bunny back.
-BUNNY: No, stop.
-(GRANNO CHUCKLES)
BUNNY: And last but not least.
Oh, what to get
for the delicate flower
who ejected me from her loins?
-Hmm.
-Oh, thank you.
Finally, something to beat
some common sense
into the lot of you.
BUNNY: So,
where's the baby mama?
-I... I'm here.
-(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
You? You're my brother's
pregnant widow.
Huh. I'm afraid
Santa forgot your gift.
It's okay.
Hang on.
BUNNY: Ian gave it to me
when I passed my A levels.
Take it, I insist.
Thank you.
Well, who wants sea bass?
-Oh, me. Me, me, please.
-LAKE: Yes.
-FELIX: I am starving.
-(LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING)
-FELIX: 20K. 20K, and in three weeks, four weeks.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
(MUSIC FADES)
So, where are you from, Stella?
I grew up in Ilford, in Essex.
Oh, dear.
More chocolate silk pie, dear?
No, thank you.
I couldn't eat another bite, um.
I should
probably call it a night.
Uh, it's been
a really long day and,
well, I shot
a fifth birthday party
at a Gymboree,
just to make some extra cash.
-I have about 100 photos to edit.
-What the fuck's a Gymboree?
I've got a confession
to make, Stella.
-I saw you earlier listening out in the hallway.
-(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
So, I know that you know
that we're hiding something.
-I wasn't--
-CAROLINE: Relax.
It's not as if a baby shower
is the secret of the century.
-(GASPS)
-(CAROLINE LAUGHS)
(SIGHS, CHUCKLES)
Oh, you...
Wow, you don't...
you don't have to do that.
Oh, no, we must celebrate you
and the little one.
It's just going to be
a family affair.
Very quiet. Low-key.
(CHUCKLES)
-(BIRDS CHIRPING)
-(INTRICATE MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
Champagne is meant
to served immediately!
This is fucking warm! Go fix it.
MRS. DEREK:
I was just telling Derek,
it's great having an excuse
for us all to get together.
-Are you planning on eating the placenta?
-(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
You look lovely.
Absolutely glowing.
DEREK: Don't be afraid of labor.
That's the easy part.
It's raising them that's hard.
-Think happy thoughts.
-(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
-(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
-(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(CAMERA CLATTERING)
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKER)
-Do you mind pouring me one of those?
-(DRINK POURING)
Sure. (CHUCKLES)
-They threw me one last month.
-(DRINK POURING)
Felt like someone ran me over,
and then dropped presents
on top of my body. (CHUCKLES)
-Yeah.
-(GLASSES CLINK)
I'm Rose. Henry's wife.
He and Ian were cousins.
Twice removed or something.
My condolences, by the way.
I can't imagine going
through this alone.
-Listen, when they tell you anything about--
-Rose, come here.
I'm being summoned.
Um, maybe we will talk again?
Oh, and don't worry
about the insect.
-It doesn't bite or anything.
-HENRY: Rose.
ROSE: Coming, darling.
Insect? What?
-(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
No offense, but...
you're going to be too heavy
for me to carry inside
if you do decide
to go into labor.
Uh, this one's got me running
about a million degrees,
so the cold water feels nice.
So I'm not the only one
that needed a breather.
(WATER RIPPLING)
I can't believe
how many people came.
-They don't even know me.
-Our family's a little weird,
but you might have
sussed that already.
But they mean well.
Come on.
-No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-STELLA: Please?
No. Okay.
Let me get my glasses.
One second.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
STELLA: Nice. One more?
-(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
-STELLA: Yes.
I think this is
my better side anyway.
(CHUCKLES)
You want a pound's worth
of free advice?
Thought the going rate
was a penny.
Yeah, well, mine's worth more.
Whatever's going to happen...
let it.
Fighting just makes it worse.
Oh, case in point.
It's time.
Come on in.
-This tradition has been in the family for generations.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Granno's done it, I've done it,
and now, it's your turn.
Just now, lie down here.
-STELLA: Really?
-CAROLINE: Mm.
(GUESTS SHUSHING)
It's nothing to be scared of.
It's just a little insect
that we're going to drop
on your belly,
and it'll land
on its back or its feet.
So, one way means a boy,
the other means a girl.
-Which is which?
-GRANNO: Hello!
-(GUESTS APPLAUD)
-(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
Are you ready?
(ALL EXCLAIM)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
Oh, I just wish
I could convince you
to stay with us longer.
I have to get back tomorrow.
I'm so behind with work.
Of course.
But I'll visit
when the baby comes.
How about a nightcap?
A virgin one
for the mama-to-be, naturally.
(CHUCKLES)
I hope you felt showered
by Cadell love today.
-Granno.
-Thank you.
CAROLINE: May this baby
be everything that we hope,
nothing more,
nothing less. Cheers.
-Cheers.
-GUESTS: Cheers.
(SLURPS SOFTLY, GULPS)
-Thank you, darling.
-My pleasure.
You've all been so generous.
I could never have afforded
most of those things on my own,
so thank you.
Well, if that's your way
of asking if we're going to fund
the baby going
forward, then... (LAUGHS)
-No, I would never ex--
-Oh darling, I'm just teasing.
Though you probably should.
And we are happy to help.
It's not always easy marrying
into the Cadell family,
but trust me,
we take care of our own.
That's very kind.
Okay.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ECHOING) I think I stood up
too quickly. (CHUCKLES)
Uh, thank you
again for everything.
Good night, everyone.
(MUSIC DISTORTS)
(ECHOING) Good luck.
(ECHOING) You too.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
-(GROANS, BREATHES SHAKILY)
-Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hey. It's okay.
I need some help here!
You have Ian's nose.
DEREK: Pre-eclampsia.
Your pressure's off the charts.
Couple that
with the loss of balance.
What does that mean?
Is the baby--
DEREK: Oh, completely fine.
(SIGHS) I... I should probably
go to a hospital.
Well, all they'd do
is run the same tests I did.
I mean, the best prescription
for pre-eclampsia
is complete rest.
Luckily, you only have
a short time till you deliver.
Derek is the top OB-GYN
in the country.
DEREK: You can get up
to go to the bathroom,
uh, shower once a day,
walk a little.
Apart from that,
you take it easy.
No cooking, no cleaning,
no strenuous exercise.
Well, I... I live alone.
Well, the last thing
we want to see is for you
to have a similar episode
on a long drive.
It could be fatal.
We could take care of her here.
I... I can't ask you to do that.
Oh, Stella,
I know that you wanna be home
where things are familiar,
but we've got to listen
to Derek.
We can be your home,
your family.
This is the last thing
that I will ever get to do
for my son.
Please, will you stay?
(REFLECTIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) Okay.
(SIGHS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(WATER GUSHING)
-(REFLECTIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENING)
CAROLINE: Stella.
Stella.
Oh! (CHUCKLES) There you are.
-Oh, Derek said it was okay to...
-Yes, no, of course.
Um, I was just wondering
if you felt like going out,
taking a walk,
getting some fresh air?
Mm. Okay.
Great.
-I'll finish. (CHUCKLES)
-Yes.
CAROLINE: So,
you've got your phone,
you've got your laptop,
extra pillows.
Is there anything else
I can get for you?
Can you get this baby
out of me faster?
-(CHUCKLES)
-No. No, no, you must never wish for that.
I mean, what if something were
to go wrong,
and then this would be
the only time
that you had with her?
It'd be irreplaceable.
Her?
-(BIRDS CHIRPING)
-(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh.
I don't suppose that, um...
Ian told you that I lost a baby.
I-- After Bunny.
She was, um, she was stillborn
and the only time
I got to spend with her
was when she was inside me.
Caroline, I'm so sorry.
It was a long time ago.
(SIGHS)
But you guys really didn't need
to go to all this trouble.
It's what families do.
Mm. My mom
was more of a "get drunk
-and miss my dance recital" type.
-Oh, no. (CHUCKLES)
Well, you know what they say,
you can't pick your family,
but you can pick your in-laws.
-Usually.
-(CHUCKLES)
And you, my dear, have...
very overprotective ones.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Sit, darling.
STELLA:
Can I ask you a question?
CAROLINE: Mm?
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Why did Ian leave home?
(SIGHS) He was in love.
She was wrong for the family,
and everyone could see that.
I'm not sure I understand.
The Cadells
are a very old family.
Some people might say
that we're set in our ways.
There definitely are
one or two requirements
that need to be met.
It's about character.
And to be a part of this family,
you might be...
called upon
to meet one or two...
obligations.
Ian struggled with that.
And if Ian had...
brought me home.
CAROLINE:
If Ian had brought you home...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
I'd have said...
that he brought someone home
who was strong enough
to do what needed to be done.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER RADIO)
-(MUSIC FADES)
-(PEN SCRIBBLES)
-(SIGH)
-(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
-(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
-Hello.
REBECCA: (OVER CELL PHONE)
Hi, this is Rebecca
from Dr. Wilkinson's office.
Your mother-in-law
called earlier,
and she wanted me
to let you know
she spoke with Dr. Cadell.
Uh, does Dr. Wilkinson
wanna see me?
REBECCA: Oh, no need.
She concurs with Dr. Cadell
that bed rest
is the right course,
and recommends
you have your baby there.
If that's what's best
for the baby.
REBECCA: Mm-hmm.
Have a nice day, my lover.
Bye.
-(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
-(SIGHS)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
-(DOOR CREAKING, OPENING)
-You must be starved.
Pretty much always.
There.
Oh, is that garlic?
Nature's purifier.
Keeps toxins
and other nasties out.
It quite potent.
I think I'll just
stick with toast.
You need protein, dear.
And garlic helps
lower blood pressure.
We want mommy
and baby healthy, don't we?
Okay.
Little stuffy in here. No.
Ah.
Now.
What are those?
Lucky charms.
Ian's grandfather,
my late husband,
brought them back from Sudan.
Gave them to me
on our first anniversary.
(SKEPTICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Now then.
(CHUCKLES)
Ta-da.
Get up, get up.
Is that for me?
Shall we see if it fits?
-I'm... I'm fine, thank you.
-Arms up.
There. Off.
This way round.
And...
there.
Oh, you look lovely.
I wore that gown
for the last weeks
of both my pregnancies,
and both my babies
were healthy and beautiful.
It's nice and cool, isn't it?
(SIGHS)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING INDISTINCTLY)
-(WOOD CREAKING)
-(METAL CLACKING)
-(SHUSHES)
-(SIGHS)
What are you doing in here?
Sorry, I know one of these
is loose as a whore's drawers.
(STELLA SIGHING)
BUNNY: Ah, there it is. Yes.
Do cigarettes go bad,
or are they like Twiglets?
It's the middle
of the night, Bunny.
I couldn't sleep.
I get lonely.
You know, it's a shame
you can't order people
like you can pizzas.
Yeah, Domino's, hi.
Yeah, it's Bunny.
I would like to order
a rugged brunette,
six feet, eight inches.
Oh, no. Those are two
separate measurements.
(CHUCKLES)
Dear old mom threatened
to send me to boarding school
if she caught me smoking again,
so Ian let me store a stash
in one of his hidey-holes.
-Did Ian say anything about me?
-That you were his best friend.
That when you were kids,
he couldn't say your name right,
-so Benny became Bunny.
-Mm.
If I could go back, I would...
blow a pack of Marlboros
in her face,
let her send me
as far away as possible.
Was it really that bad
growing up in this family?
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
Not if you toed the party line.
-(LIGHTER FLICKING)
-Fucking...
Well, I guess
your mother has high standards.
(CHUCKLES)
Like with that girlfriend
Ian brought home.
Please, please.
No, Ian would have
brought back a clan member
before he'd
subject a girl to this.
But your mom said he did.
Did she?
Oh, well, I'm sure she's right.
Always is.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
Breakfast time.
The most important
meal of the day.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, I... I don't
usually do salmon
first thing in the morning.
Fish wards off the evil eye.
And the food isn't just for you,
it's to protect
that little one inside you.
Um, no, really. I... I...
Being a mom means
putting aside your own needs
-for the sake of others.
-No, really.
GRANNO: Well...
if you aren't willing to eat
what the baby needs,
maybe you're just not hungry.
We'll try again later.
(SIGHS SHAKILY)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
LAKE: Stella?
Darling, you decent?
Yeah, come in.
(SHUSHES)
Double cheeseburger and fries.
Granno means well.
She just gets a little hardcore
with this woo-woo business.
Too many wellness podcasts
or something.
Mm. You're a lifesaver.
God, these things are hideous.
I bet
they're giving you nightmares.
-It's fine. (CHUCKLES)
-LAKE: You're sweet.
Going to have to suppress
that urge
if you want to survive
in this family, though.
Ugh.
You don't have to do that.
And you didn't
have to get me food.
What's it like?
What? Being pregnant?
Having life growing inside you,
feeling it turn, kick.
It's weird.
-Weird?
-STELLA: It's, uh...
Ooh.
Hello. Do you wanna feel?
(EXCLAIMS)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
STELLA: Oh. Oh.
Okay. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
So, that's what it's like?
No, don't move.
I'm just processing.
(PAPER CRUMPLING)
Feeding her crap.
Doesn't take a genius
to figure out why.
Oh, I'm just being nice
to the preggo.
Yeah, for the last few days
you've been saying
Granno's old wives' tales
are crazy talk.
What's gonna happen
is gonna happen.
Can't change that.
Funny there are no
old husband tales.
Guess everybody knows
they're useless.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Maybe it is all dumb luck,
I don't know,
but I am sick of waiting.
I like you like this,
viciously optimistic.
And I like it
when you're not being a--
(GASPS, CHUCKLES)
Once it's finally safe
for us to try...
I'll fuck you so fast
your uterus will spin.
(INTIMATE BREATHING)
-Maybe I'll put two in there.
-Oh, fuck that's hot.
(LAKE MOANS)
-I fucking love you.
-(SLAPS)
Come and I'll cut your dick off.
(MOANING CONTINUES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(FAINT SOBS)
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
CAROLINE: No. No.
You won't take my baby.
No. No.
No. You won't take my baby. No.
(SOBS) No.
No. (SOBS)
(BABY CRYING)
You will not take my baby.
Caroline.
You're not taking my baby.
You are not taking my baby.
(WHIMPERS)
Mom. Oh, God!
-Hey. Hey.
-(CAROLINE SCREAMS)
LAKE: (SHUSHES) It's okay.
(SHUSHES)
Your babies are right here.
CAROLINE: No, don't take it.
What's going on?
It's your mom.
She's sleepwalking again.
Okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
We're here. We're here.
(CAROLINE SOBS)
GRANNO: Caroline.
-(GASPS)
-(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
CAROLINE:
Was I sleepwalking again?
Did I do it again?
-I'm so sorry.
-(BUNNY SHUSHING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(TILE CLANKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSING, LOCKING)
If the wind changes,
you'll stay like that, Granno.
-(LAUGHS MISCHIEVOUSLY)
-(GRANNO CHUCKLES)
It's 10:00 a.m.
I know.
We're starting late today.
(GRANNO SIGHING)
-What's she doing?
-I have no idea.
STELLA: Ian.
Lake. Benjamin.
The stillborn baby.
Stillborn baby.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
Another stillborn baby.
I only need 10K.
Make an OnlyFans.
They've probably
never seen balls that small.
Oh. (CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY)
What's going on in here?
FELIX: Baby mama drama.
This looks bad. Is it bad?
Where did she get
the phone from?
LAKE: We could make
her a sleepy drink,
take the phone away
while she's passed out.
Maybe some tea, lemonade.
Bunny, what's the best way
of hiding the taste of roofies?
I don't know.
What do you use on Felix?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
What did you drug her with
at the shower?
I don't think she's gonna go
for a midday mocktail.
I mean, if we knock her out,
she's gonna be a tad suspicious
when she wakes up
and everything's gone.
INFLUENCER: And so for today's
super stealth life hack,
we're gonna revive a phone
with no charger.
The red wire is for positive,
and the black is for negative.
So you just
line each of the wires up
with the charging points,
and you'll find that it...
Stop it.
Just stop it, stop it...
-No, this is the max. Hey.
-...stop it.
No, no, no. Don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't, don't.
Granno. No, no, no, let's
just bring this down, okay?
You're so extra.
INFLUENCER: Wires--
(LAPTOP KEYS CLACKING RAPIDLY)
Oh!
And like that, poof, it's gone.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(EXHALES)
(CHUCKLES)
(SOBS)
(CONTINUES TO SOB)
IAN: Explain it to me again.
CAROLINE: Oh, Ian,
what else do you want me to say?
IAN: I remember the night
that she was born.
I remember waking up
and going down the hall
into the nursery,
and you were standing
over her cot,
strangling her.
You were crying and...
CAROLINE: You were a child.
You couldn't possibly remember--
IAN: And Granno
was shouting at you
to do it faster, squeeze harder.
I remember it all.
CAROLINE: You just
don't want to believe me.
I want you to tell me
the real reason
that you killed my baby sister.
CAROLINE: So you prefer
to think of us as psychopathic,
-random baby murderers?
-Not random.
One child each generation.
(THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SHARP EXHALE)
(BREATHES HEAVILY, SNIFFLES)
(DOOR SQUEAKING)
(EXHALING SHARPLY)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(FAINT BREATHING)
I was just looking for you.
Were you?
Yeah, I wanted
to borrow a cardigan.
I was gonna get some fresh air.
Go back to your room, Stella.
Take her back to bed.
No. Hey. Get... Get off.
FELIX: Come on.
(STELLA GRUNTING)
LAKE: Come on,
you stupid bitch.
(STELLA GRUNTING)
Bunny, do something.
Grab her legs, for fuck's sake.
(HITS)
-Bitch.
-Fuck you! (GRUNTS)
You stop
or I will tie you to the bed.
There are people
that know I'm here.
The doctor at the health clinic.
Oh, that was me.
Sorry, my lover.
Hi, this is Rebecca
from Dr. Wilkinson's office.
Your mother-in-law called,
and the doctor
agrees with Dr. Cadell.
Leave us.
-I need a moment.
-(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(STELLA BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR CLOSING)
We're not monsters, Stella.
We don't want to hurt you.
You killed your own child.
Yes, sadly.
And I will kill yours
if I have to.
(BREATHES NERVOUSLY)
No, Stella,
you deserve the truth.
What we know of it anyway.
I'm not sure anybody can really
remember the details anymore.
(SIGHS) But the story goes,
hundreds of years ago...
a Cadell ancestor took the baby
of a pagan girl
who was camping on the property,
and then they wanted
to raise this wretched creature
in the light of Jesus
and blah, blah, blah.
And then her family retaliated,
and they put a curse
on the Cadell family.
(WHISPER OF THE CURSE)
And the curse was
that once a generation...
a baby would be born...
that was pure evil.
And if that baby
was allowed to live,
death would follow it
everywhere it went...
until the whole
of civilization...
was wiped out.
Yes. I do know how that sounds.
Yeah, well,
that's very comforting.
I was in the bedroom
down the hallway
when Granno
first told me that story.
(EXHALING SHARPLY)
Yeah, I mean, I thought
they were all completely crazy.
I mean, what a ridiculous tale.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
And then...
you know, I had Lake
and Ian and Bunny,
and they were all
perfectly normal.
Well, at least
I thought they were.
My husband Michael
wanted to stop there...
but I had this dream...
of this perfect little family.
Two little girls,
two little boys.
You see, only someone
in the Cadell bloodline
can actually see
what the baby is.
So when they told me.
When they told me what she was.
I didn't believe them...
because to me she looked...
she looked perfect.
And so I fought,
I fought to keep
my newborn baby alive,
and I did it. I... I...
I did it for six hours.
And in that short
period of time...
my husband got a knife,
went into the bathroom
and hacked his own throat out.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
That's when I realized
they were telling me the truth.
That my own stubbornness...
had killed my husband.
The man I loved.
So some demented
folktale from centuries ago
made you baby killers?
I am so sorry
that happened to you, Caroline.
But it doesn't mean
your baby was...
Yes, it does, Stella,
because I didn't listen.
And it doesn't matter
what you saw on Ian's phone
because he clearly
believed it, too,
or at least he couldn't
prove otherwise.
He didn't want a baby, Stella.
Don't you get it? He was scared.
He watched his own mother
strangle his baby sister
to death.
He was trying to protect you
from ever having
to make that choice.
And then you told him
you were pregnant.
And clearly...
he couldn't handle
the possibilities.
No.
Listen to me.
If your baby is normal,
I will let you leave here
safe and sound...
and I will give you enough money
to live a comfortable life.
I promise.
And if it's not a normal baby?
Ian would never forgive you.
Yes.
Actually, I think
he would, Stella.
(STELLA SOBBING)
(DOOR CLOSING, LOCKING)
(CONTINUES TO SOB)
(EXHALES THROUGH MOUTH)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING) No.
(OBJECTS SHATTERING)
(SCREAMS)
Well, she'll have to accept it
sooner or later.
There hasn't been one
in over 30 years.
It's got to be her.
-Not necessarily.
-(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
Another fetus there is.
-Cousin Rose?
-Mm.
I don't know.
I think she's too dull
to squeeze out a demon.
-(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
-Oh.
Well, we'll know soon enough.
According to
the Cadell family text,
her water's just broke.
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
FELIX: Okay.
You be nice...
I'll be nice.
(SIGHING)
Stella.
I signed the Cadell
confidentiality clause
on my wedding night.
They said you might
have to murder a baby,
and you still said, "I do"?
To be fair, the NDA came
with a million-pound payout, so.
So it's just
about money for you?
I've been poor,
and I've been rich,
and I won't be ashamed
for having a preference.
You can't really believe--
Lake believes.
Yeah, but she's fucking crazy.
-(SLAP)
-(STELLA GRUNTING)
That's my fucking wife.
She needs me...
and I'll always
be there for her.
STELLA: Does she? Need you?
(DEBRIS CRUNCHING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Oh, I forgot.
Granno said
I could make you an offer.
A compensation package of sorts
for eating your meal
like a good girl.
You can have
someone new to talk to.
Hmm? Interested?
Oh, whatever. Just make up
your mind. Let us know.
(DOOR CLOSING, LOCKING)
(SOBS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROSE GRUNTING)
Ian never wanted me
to meet his family,
and now I know why.
You know, he would kill them
before he let them hurt me
or our baby.
How can anyone
believe this crazy story
about pagan curses?
It's not just a story to them.
Do you remember there was
an old woman at your shower?
She had a patch on one eye.
Well, let me guess,
a baby gouged it out.
She did it herself.
-(SCOFFS)
-ROSE: (OVER SCREEN) The night her baby was born,
she tried to run away with it.
They found her in a motorway
service station ten miles away,
and she used a plastic spoon.
STELLA: So they say.
So they say.
(ROSE BREATHES HEAVILY)
You tried to tell me
at the shower, didn't you?
Have they convinced you, Rose?
Do you really believe them?
Listen to me. Look at me.
There is nothing wrong
with either of our babies.
We have to stick together.
Help the other
if the opportunity
presents itself.
Okay?
Okay.
(SCREAMS) Help!
Somebody help me.
What is it? You okay?
I think there's something wrong
with the baby.
I need to go to hospital.
Stella, I can't.
Bunny, my baby could be dying.
Please.
-What's happening?
-Mum, she's fucking bleeding.
Look. Look, look.
Fucking look, look, look.
Okay, are you in pain?
I read something
in the baby book,
something about
a placenta previa.
Caroline, I really think
I need to go to the hospital.
Yeah, that is a possibility.
Let's, uh...
(CONTINUES GROANING)
Another possibility
is that you cut yourself
and smeared the blood.
Go, Bunny, go!
(STELLA SCREAMING)
(STELLA SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
Lamb stew.
We just tied
a pregnant woman to a bed.
Couldn't we at least
give her a pizza?
Lambs have been a symbol
of purity and protection
for thousands of years.
Hand me that garlic.
We're not trying to torture her.
That's what my Michael
said to me about you.
How did that end?
This isn't torture.
Torture is
what you went through,
laboring for hours
only to give birth to a monster.
Losing your husband, my son,
because you weren't
strong enough
to put an end
to the wretched thing
when it first drew breath.
If a little torture could have
spared you that fate...
how much would you
have happily endured?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
The real tragedy of all this
is I'm really a fantastic cook.
When all this is over,
I'll serve you my duck confit
with Sarladaise potatoes.
When this is over,
you'll be in a cell...
along with the rest
of your lunatic family.
Seventy-odd years ago,
when her baby was born wrong,
my own mother
didn't wail and whine, "Why me?"
She carried the creature
to the bathtub
and did what needed to be done.
She sounds like
a regular psychopath.
(CUTLERY CLANKING)
Open wide.
I see.
Well, if you still refuse
to eat the food
I have so lovingly prepared
to protect your child...
there are other ways.
The demons that worm their ways
into our babies
like things to be warm.
One way we can protect ourselves
is to make our bodies
as inhospitable as possible.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(WINDOWS OPENING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Please. Please don't do this.
GRANNO: It's nothing
compared to the pain
of losing a child.
(GROANS)
Cold is what you need
to protect your baby.
Ian's child.
My first and possibly
only great-grandchild.
It's not Ian's baby.
I had an affair. It's not his.
She's lying.
No! No, I'm not. I swear!
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
It's what we fought about
the night he died.
Oh, Stella,
I see the pain in your eyes
when you talk about him.
You didn't cheat on my son.
You loved him,
like I loved his father.
-(SOBS)
-(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROSE SCREAMS)
(PANTS) It's too hard I can't.
-DEREK: Nearly there.
-ROSE: Oh, God.
-DEREK: Push again.
-(ROSE GROANS, STRAINS)
-DEREK: I can see the head.
-(ROSE PANTS) Oh, come out!
DEREK: Keep pushing.
A big one now.
(ROSE SCREAMS)
-(BABY CRYING)
-(ROSE PANTS)
Oh, God.
-(SOBS)
-(BABY CRYING)
Is my baby normal?
Just tell me. (PANTS)
Henry!
(SOBS) Is he? Is he?
-Look at him.
-(BABY CRYING)
(GASPS)
Have you ever seen
such a beautiful boy?
ROSE: Oh, my God. (SOBS)
BUNNY: Congrats, Henry.
Doesn't mean anything.
Stella could still have
a normal baby.
It means
the interventions worked.
The food, and the cold,
and the lucky charms,
they protected Rose's baby,
and they'll work
for our baby too.
(GROANS, SNIFFLES)
Lake.
Blimey. Overreact much?
(BABY COOS)
-(CRIES)
-(ROBS)
Bunny.
ROSE: Hi.
(SOBS)
(DOOR CLOSES, LOCKS)
I have been waiting
my whole life.
She's 20-fucking-three.
Oh, sweetheart,
she's a fertile myrtle.
What do you wanna bet
that Rose is pregnant again
this time next year?
-And maybe that'll be the one.
-Newsflash, Mother,
I'm running out of time.
If Stella isn't carrying it,
then that is it for me.
Boo-hoo,
your eggs are drying up.
That's our brother's wife.
Ian's kid, upstairs.
Do you even care?
You know what?
I don't think you get a vote.
A vote? What about reality?
Would it kill you to fuck
a few online crazy slags?
Spit out a few random sprogs
just to level the odds a bit?
BUNNY: Okay. Just FYI, uh,
only Nazis and the elderly
use online dating sites.
Also, not a big fan
-of the lady parts.
-Oh, please.
You can just take one
for the team, as the Yanks say.
-Did you really just say that to me?
--I did, actually. Yes, I did.
We don't do this.
This is not who we are.
(SCOFFS) Yeah, no,
we're one big happy family.
Hard to believe Ian legged it.
Well, I think
we should roll the dice.
I'd risk it to have a little
version of us running around.
Can you get out
of my fucking face?
I actually cannot stand
to look at you.
We need each other,
Lake. (CHUCKLES)
LAKE: I never needed you, Felix.
I like that you follow me around
like a little lost
pathetic puppy,
but honestly,
if you disappeared tomorrow,
I would go to the pound,
and I would get another one.
HENRY: So proud of you both.
Let me grab a shower
and I'll bring you
something to eat.
Love, do you mind?
Oh, right. Yeah.
-(ROSE SIGHS)
-Hold on, darling. Sorry.
-(SIGHS)
-I know.
ROSE: Oh, thank you.
Hi, bubba. Ah.
Rose! (BREATHES SHAKILY)
You can get to a phone now.
(SOBS) Pl... Please.
You... You ha...
You have to help me.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Call... Call the police
to help me.
You... You can help
get me out.
Please help. Call them.
Please. Rose. Ro...
(STELLA GASPS)
(SCREAMS) No!
No! (SOBS)
No! (SOBS) Get me out!
(CROW CAWS)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
Thought you might like a wash.
Here we go.
You tell me if...
if the water's warm enough.
Doesn't matter.
CAROLINE: Ah, I see.
The nihilistic phase.
I remember that.
Why keep going?
If the family's cursed,
why keep having babies?
I'd say within
the last 100 years,
the children have regularly
survived to adulthood.
I mean,
the human need to procreate,
it's profound...
even when your children grow up
and... break your heart.
There's no such thing
as a happy family, Stella.
Not really.
Every family's screwed up
one way or the other.
I mean, look at your own mother.
She took liquor
over her own daughter.
My husband's family...
(SIGHS)
...it's a less common problem,
but trust me,
it all comes out in the wash.
(STRAINS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANS, GASPS)
(GROANS)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
Help me.
Uh, I'll get Granno.
(GROANS, BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
Where's your brother?
He went for a walk.
Well, can you find him?
We need him here.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
If you want to keep the entity
from taking root inside you,
we have to make your body
as inhospitable as possible.
A place of unbearable pain.
(GRUNTS)
That's already happening.
Oh, child,
there's always more pain.
(SOBS)
-Now...
-(GASPS)
...Ian's granddad
had this made
for our second anniversary
to ward off the evil.
(CHAIN RATTLES)
It's heavy.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Can you pass me Ian's pen?
I just wanna
feel him close to me.
If it helps.
(GRUNTS, EXHALES SHARPLY)
All this will be over soon.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
GRANNO: Now.
(GROANS)
GRANNO: Ah.
(CHAIN RATTLES)
-(SOBS)
-GRANNO: Ah.
(STELLA GROANS)
GRANNO: Now,
are you ready?
-(GROANS)
-Ah.
-(STELLA SCREAMS)
-GRANNO: Ah!
Ooh!
And you're...
(SCREAMS)
-...good!
-(STELLA CRIES)
GRANNO: And
more!
(GROANS)
Good.
-More.
-(SCREAMS)
GRANNO: Good.
And more.
Good girl.
-(SCREAMS, WHIMPERS)
-GRANNO: More?
(STELLA SCREAMS)
More?
(GRUNTS)
-(SOBS)
-(GRANNO GROANS)
(PANTS)
(GRANNO GRUNTS, GASPS)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(GROANS, STRAINS)
(GRANNO THUDS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
(SNIFFLES)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
LAKE: Oh, no. This is on.
This is on. Good.
Did you find him?
He's on his way up.
-CAROLINE: Where's Felix?
-LAKE: Why?
You need someone to stand around
and be useless?
How do I turn
this heart monitor on?
Where's the manual
to this thing?
Is that working?
Oh, I don't think it is.
LAKE: Well, we need to know.
I couldn't work it.
I can't even work this.
When was the last time
I turned on a heart monitor?
-(DOOR OPENS)
-BUNNY: Mother?
Mother!
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Bunny, I thought
I told you not to leave.
BUNNY:
I can't t do this anymore.
-CAROLINE: Can't do what then?
-BUNNY: This!
This! I can't do this anymore!
Bunny, this is our lot in life.
You can't let your emotions
get the best of you right now.
BUNNY: There's not much chance
of that with you!
Darling, you smell
like a distillery.
Was this really
the time to be drinking?
BUNNY: Yes! Actually, yes.
CAROLINE: Okay. Go.
Go get yourself cleaned up
right now.
I need you in the birthing room.
Go! Clean yourself up! Now!
(DOOR OPENS)
(BUNNY MUTTERING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY, SNIFFLES)
(GROANS)
(INHALES SHARPLY, GROANS)
(SNIFFLES)
(GROANS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
LAKE: Is it even plugged in?
She can literally
give birth at any second.
This is so stressful.
Where is the blood monitor?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(GRUNTS, SNIFFLES)
LAKE: (SCREAMS) She's...
-Oh, God!
-BUNNY: What's going on?
(GROANS)
LAKE: Granno! She's dead!
CAROLINE: Lake! Get the gun.
She can't have gone far.
(STELLA PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
She's down here!
(STELLA GROANS, GASPS)
She was a sweet, old lady.
I guess I missed
that part of her. (GASPS)
Let's get her up
to the birthing room right now.
No, the baby is coming now!
(GASPS)
Okay, let's...
let's put her down.
-We need to put her down somewhere.
--Put her on the table!
-(GROANS)
-Yeah.
-Were you gonna help or what?
-Well, let's get her comfortable.
-She's in fucking pain, all right?
-LAKE: Good!
-BUNNY: Fuck off!
-(GROANS)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
Down, down, down,
down, down, down, down.
-(GROANS)
-Okay. There.
How far away is Cousin Derek?
I... I don't...
At least two hours away.
Okay, well, you just get
some towels or something.
Be useful for once. Please!
-Oh! Me be--
-Fuck off!
-Oh, well, that's fine.
-It's okay.
STELLA: You have to
get me out of here.
Please. You don't have to listen
to what she says.
-You have to. please.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Please, you don't have to listen to her!
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I can't. I can't.
Bunny, go. Go wash your hands.
-(GROANS)
-Wait. You're joking!
I'm not delivering
this fucking baby!
Go and wash your hands!
Oh, yes,
I think she is fully dilated.
I can see the top
of the head, so, yes.
Yep, she's having one right now.
-(EXHALES SHARPLY)
-CAROLINE: Bunny!
Bunny!
(GROANS)
Okay, So you have to
take the head out gently.
You don't pull,
you just cradle it.
-(SOBS, WHIMPERS)
-BUNNY: Oh, my God.
Keep pushing, Stella.
Keep pushing.
(GROANS, SOBS)
Oh, shit,
is this really happening?
BUNNY: You're doing really
fucking well, uh, I think.
Or I can't tell. I can't tell.
-CAROLINE: Keep pushing, Stella.
-(GROANS)
Um, no, no, I ca... I can't.
No! Please!
Please don't leave me.
-Please don't.
-I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-CAROLINE: Benjamin, no!
-Get the fuck off me!
-CAROLINE: No!
-Lake, get in there.
-No. Fuck that.
I am not a Cadell!
I am not of the bloodline!
I cannot do this!
I swear to God, I'm going
to vomit all over this kid.
It's coming!
-It's coming! It's coming! Push!
-(GROANS)
-It's coming. Push, push!
-(SCREAMS)
Push!
-(SOBS)
-LAKE: That's it!
(GASPS, BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BABY CRIES)
(SOBS)
-(BABY CRIES)
-What is it?
What is it? What is it?
What is it?
It's fine. She's fine.
-No. She's just like Rose's baby.
-CAROLINE: I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry, Stella.
-No.
-I'm sorry. Cut the cord, Lake.
-(BABY CRIES)
That's your niece.
That's Ian's...
It's Ian's daughter!
It's Ian's daughter! (SOBS)
No, don't. What are you doing?
She's just a baby.
Why can't you see
she's a normal baby?
Please. She's...
she's a normal baby.
Is it really? Are you sure?
I can't even describe it.
I'm so sorry, Stella.
I'm sorry, but she...
she is. Maybe...
maybe you should do it yourself.
Give yourself closure.
Is that what you felt when
you strangled your own baby?
Closure?
Oh, she won't do it, Mum.
She doesn't believe.
-But it is her baby.
-No, she can't see what it really is.
-Neither of you can see it.
-But it's her baby!
-Just fucking kill it!
-Quiet!
This is insanity!
This is some sheer psychosis.
There is nothing wrong
with my baby!
Yes. Stella, there is.
You're just fucked in the head
because you killed
your own daughter!
And you want me to do the same
so you feel justified.
I did what needed to be done.
Bullshit! You're full of shit!
We're gonna pour some whiskey.
We're gonna save the world
from going to hell
for the next 20 years,
and then I will fuck
my very dumb husband, okay?
-(BABY CRIES)
-(GASPS)
No! No! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop. (SOBS)
I'll do it.
It sh... it should be me.
-(SOBS) I'm... I'm her mother.
-(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
STELLA: I'll do it. (SNIFFLES)
You s... you said it.
It's closure. It's closure.
Let her do it.
Don't fucking touch me.
Are you okay?
I'm not fucking okay, Caroline.
(BABY CRIES)
No!
Get the fuck away from my baby.
Stella, don't do this.
Ian was afraid of this.
He knew that something
could go wrong with the baby.
Why do you think he took
the coward's way out?
He wouldn't.
Oh, don't tell me
it didn't occur to you
-that's why he crashed his truck.
-No!
CAROLINE: Stella, he was weak!
You're strong.
You can finish this!
I'll finish your daughter
if you don't get
the fuck away from my baby!
Try me.
CAROLINE: Oh, God.
-(GASPS)
-Oh, shit.
Felix, get the gun from her.
Yeah, I don't think so.
What?
I've made a decision,
or rather I've come
to a realization.
Felix, get the fucking gun!
You are a small-hearted shrew
who is incapable of love
and unworthy of it.
No allowance is worth
sharing your bed!
-Oh, you're a fucking moron.
-See, this is what I'm talking about.
-You never respected me.
-Now is not the time!
Shut the fuck up!
You enable her.
I'm so done
with this whole fucking family.
Felix, listen to me. It's over.
Her baby's the one
with the curse.
We can finally get pregnant now.
FELIX: Lake, Lake, Lake,
any child that comes out
of your womb
is guaranteed to be cursed,
so I think
I'm gonna have to pass.
Goodbye.
Congratulations,
your baby looks like an angel.
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(SCREAMS, GROANS)
That's how it feels.
(BREATHES HEAVILY, GRUNTS)
-(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
-(BABY CRIES)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
-(LOVINGLY) Oh, no. (SHUSHES)
-(BABY CRIES)
Oh...
-(SOBS)
(SHUSHES)
(SNIFFLES)
(SOBS)
(BABY COOS)
(CAR LOCK BEEPS)
-(THUNDER RUMBLING)
-(BABY COOS)
(CRIES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROAN)
(STELLA GASPS)
(GASPS)
Let her go!
CAROLINE: Bunny?
Just look at yourself!
This is insane!
You, Granno, this entire family!
You... you... you ruined
all of our fucking lives
-with this bullshit!
-Bunny, this is real!
-This is real, Bunny!
-Mum. Mum!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
Are you okay?
Not really.
But she is.
(BABY COOS)
Your niece, she's perfect.
(SOBS)
The rest of the Cadell clan
will come looking for you.
For... for the baby.
And there's enough jewelry,
cash in the house for you...
for you... for you both.
You... you can disappear.
There's a safe
in the family study.
I left it open for you.
Come with us.
I can't.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Well, you should
at least meet her first.
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
-(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(BABY COOS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
What?
Go stand over there.
-STELLA: Bunny, what--
-Go and stand over there!
-That's my baby!
-No, that's not a baby.
That... That's... Oh, my God.
My family was right! It's real.
It's so fucking real.
-(GUN COCKS)
-Mum was right. It's fucking real! (GRUNTS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
-(GASPS)
-You'll never make it on your own!
-(SCREAMS)
-(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
-(MUSIC FADES)
-(BABY CRIES)
-(SHUSHES)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(BABY CRIES)
(MUSIC FADES)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
I hope you enjoyed
your stay with us.
Please come again.
I will. Thank you.
(BABY CRIES)
Oh, if I may say,
you have a beautiful baby.
(BABY COOS)
(MUSIC FADES)
-(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
-(WHISPER OF THE CURSE)
(BABY COOS)
(MUSIC FADES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)